(Raj:)Okay. Uh...
Oh, hey, how about her?
Sure, if he wants to spend years
doing her homework...
(Leonard:)...while she drinks herself into a stupor
with nonfat White Russians.
And you're holding her head
while she's puking...
...and wishes more guys were like you.
(Leonard:)She gets into Cornell,
because you wrote her essay.
(Leonard:)And you drive up to visit her one weekend
and she acts like she doesn't know you.
(Raj:)Okay, so not her either.
(Raj:)How about her?
(Howard:)Interesting, kind of pretty, a little chubby,
so probably low self-esteem.
(Leonard:)I think that's our girl.
(Leonard:)One of us should go talk to her.
(Raj:)I can't talk to her, you do it.
(Leonard:)I can't just go up and talk to her.
(Leonard:)Howard, you talk to her.
I don't know, she'll never go for the kid
once she gets a peek at this.
(Raj:)In India, this would be simpler.
Five minutes with her dad, 20 goats
and a laptop, and we'd be done.
(Leonard:)Well, we're not in India.
(Raj:)Why don't we do it your way, then?